Guide to the New-York Historical Society Geographic Images Collection circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI: American Views (includes New York State)
  - Subseries VIA: AMERICAN VIEWS - BOXED MATERIAL
    - New York-Hudson River-Mountains-Storm King (Offsite-box 20, Folder 10)
    - New York-Huntington (Offsite-box 20, Folder 11)
    - New York-Hurley (folder 1 of 4) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 12)
    - New York-Hurley (folder 2 of 4) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 13)
    - New York-Hurley (folder 3 of 4) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 14)
    - New York-Hurley (folder 4 of 4) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 15)
    - New York-Hyde Park-general (Offsite-box 20, Folder 16)
    - New York-Hyde Park-Roosevelt House and Presidential Library (Offsite-box 20, Folder 17)
    - New York - I (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
    - New York-Irvington (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2)
    - New York-Ithaca (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
    - New York-J, circa 1880s-1966 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
      Includes: printed engraving of Elias Hicks residence at Jericho (1880s?); postcard, drawing of Old St. John's, Johnstown, NY (1910), gift of John Pierce, 1910; photo, frog pond at Jamaica, L.I. (1931), from E.B. Child collection; photo, Indian Village at Jones Beach, L.I. (1935), believed to be taken by donor's unnamed father, gift of Susan Kelso Malone, 20190; photo, covered bridge, Jay, NY (1953); photo, covered bridge over Ballenskill River, Jacksonville, NY (1955); postcard, Osceola Beach and Picnic Grove, Jefferson Valley, NY (1966); photo of drawing from N-YHS collection of Jessup's Landing (undated).
    - New York-K (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
    - New York-Kaaterskill Falls (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
    - New York-Kinderhook (Offsite-box 21, Folder 7)
    - New York-Kingston-general- folder 1 of 2 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
    - New York-Kingston-general (folder 2 of 2) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 9)
    - New York-Kingston (Senate House) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 10)
    - New York-LA - LZ (Offsite-box 21, Folder 11)
    - New York-Lakes-A - Z (Offsite-box 21, Folder 12)
    - New York-Lakes-Lake Champlain (Offsite-box 21, Folder 13)
    - New York-Lakes-Kaaterskill Lake (Offsite-box 21, Folder 14)
    - New York-Lakes-Lake George (photos) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 15)
    - New York-Lakes-Lake George (prints) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 16)
    - New York-Lakes-Lake Mohegan (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
    - New York-Lakes-Little Falls on the Mohawk River (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
    - New York-Lakes-Little Seneca River (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
    - New York-Lakes-Mohonk Lake (Offsite-box 22, Folder 12)
    - New York-Locust Valley (Offsite-box 22, Folder 4)
    - New York-Long Island-unidentified towns (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
    - New York-Luzerne (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - New York-M (Offsite-box 22, Folder 8)
    - New York-Marbletown (Offsite-box 22, Folder 9)
    - New York-Massapequa (Offsite-box 22, Folder 10)
    - New York-Mohawk (River and Valley) (Offsite-box 22, Folder 11)
    - New York-Montauk (Offsite-box 22, Folder 13)
    - New York-Mount Vernon (Offsite-box 22, Folder 14)
    - New York-Mount Sinai (Offsite-box 22, Folder 15)
    - New York-N (Offsite-box 22, Folder 16)
    - New York-Newburgh-general: photos (Offsite-box 22, Folder 17)
    - New York-Newburgh-general: prints (Offsite-box 22, Folder 18)
    - New York-Newburgh-Washington's Headquarters (Offsite-box 22, Folder 19)
    - New York-New Paltz (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - New York-New Rochelle (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - New York-New Windsor (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New York-Niagara Falls-general (folder 1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - New York-Niagara Falls-general (folder 2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York-Niagara Falls-photos (folder 1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - New York-Niagara Falls-photos (folder 2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - New York-Niagara Falls-prints (folder 1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - New York-Niagara Falls-prints (folder 2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - New York-North Tarrytown (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - New York-North Peekskill (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - New York-Nyack (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - New York-O (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - New York-Oakdale (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - New York-Ogdensburg (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - New York-Ossining (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - New York-Oswego (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - New York-Oyster Bay-general (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - New York-Oyster Bay-Sagamore Hill-Theodore Roosevelt residence (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - New York-P (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - New York-Peekskill (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - New York-Pelham Manor (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - New York-Poughkeepsie (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - New York-Q (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - New York-Quaker Hill (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - New York-R (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York-Rochester-general (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - New York-Rochester-Genesse Falls (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - New York-Rose (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - New York-Roslyn (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - New York-Rye (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - New York-SA - SN (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - New York-Saranac Lake (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - New York-Saratoga Springs-general (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - New York-Saratoga Springs-Congress Hall (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - New York-Saugerties (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - New York-Scarsdale (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - New York-Schenectady (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - New York-Schoharie (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - New York-Schuylerville (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - New York-Seager (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - New York-Setauket (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - New York-Sharon (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - New York-Shavertown (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - New York-Long Beach (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - New York-Shushan (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - New York-SO - SZ (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - New York-Southampton (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - New York-Stoneridge (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - New York-Stony Brook-general (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - New York-Stony Brook-Hercules Figurehead (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - New York-Stony Point (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - New York-Syracuse (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - New York-T (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - New York-Tappan-general (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - New York-Tappan-Washington's Headquarters (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - New York-Tarrytown-general (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - New York-Tarrytown-Sunnyside-Washington Irving residence (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - New York-Thousand Islands (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - New York-Troy (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - New York-U (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - New York-Utica (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - New York-V (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - New York-Valhalla (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - New York-W (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - New York-Watertown (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - New York-Westchester County (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - New York-West Point-General (prints) (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - New York-West Point-General (photos) (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - New York-West Point-Fort Putnam (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - New York-West Point-Kosciuzko Garden and Tomb (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - New York-West Point-Military Academy (folder 1 of 4) (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - New York-West Point-Military Academy (folder 2 of 4) (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - New York-West Point-Military Academy (folder 3 of 4) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - New York-West Point-Military Academy (folder 4 of 4) (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - New York-White Plains (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - New York-Yonkers-general (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - New York-Yonkers-Phillipse Manor House (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - New York-Yorktown (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - New York-Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - New York-Unidentified (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - New York-Hudson River-General views (folder 1 of 3) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina- A - Z (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - North Carolina-Asheville (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - North Carolina-Edenton (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina-New Bern (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - North Carolina-Raleigh (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - North Dakota-A - Z (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Ohio-A - Z (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Ohio-Cincinnati (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Ohio-Cleveland-General (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Ohio-Cleveland-Buildings (general) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Ohio-Cleveland-Western Reserve Historical Society (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Ohio-Cleveland-Churches (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Ohio-Cleveland-Schools and Universities (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Ohio-Columbus (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Ohio-Toledo (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Oklahoma-A - Z (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Oklahoma-Gutherie (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Oklahoma-Opening of the Cherokee Strip (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Oregon-A - Z (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania-A - L (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania-Conestoga/Susquehanna area -- Indian Point (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania-Delaware Water Gap (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania-Ephrata (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania-Gettysburg (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania-Hometown (railroad) (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania-Johnstown (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania-Lancaster (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania-M - R (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania-New Hope (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-General (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Bridges (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Street Scenes (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Brochures - historical (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Buildings (General) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Buildings (Banks) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Buildings (Carpenter's Hall) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Buildings (Independence Hall/State House) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Churches (General) (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Churches (Christ Church) (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Colleges, Schools (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Institutions (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Museums and Libraries (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Fairmont Park (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Penitentiaries (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Residences-General (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Residences-Benedict Arnold (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Residences-William Penn (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Water Views (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-World's Fair 1876 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania-Pittsburgh (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania-Roadside America Village (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania-S - Z (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania-Schuylkill (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania-Valley Forge (General) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania-Valley Forge (Washington's Headquarters) (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania-York (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania-Miscellaneous (general) (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania-Miscellaneous (railroads) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania-Miscellaneous (rivers) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania-Philadelphia-Residences-Chew House (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Rhode Island-A - Z (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Rhode Island-Block Island (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Rhode Island-Newport-Beach Views (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Rhode Island-Newport-Buildings (Deaf and Dumb Asylum) (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Rhode Island-Newport-Buildings (Old Stone Tower/Mill) (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Rhode Island-Newport-Residences (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Rhode Island-Newport-Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Rhode Island-Providence (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Rhode Island-Wakefield (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - South Carolina-A - Z (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee-A - Z (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee-Nashville (general) (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee-Nashville (The Hermitage) (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Texas-A - Z (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Texas-San Antonio (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Utah-A - Z (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Utah-Great Salt Lake (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Utah-Salt Lake City-Street Views (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Utah-Salt Lake City-Temple and Tabernacle (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Utah-Salt Lake City-General (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Utah-Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Vermont-A - Z (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Vermont-Bennington (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Vermont-Burlington (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Vermont-Plymouth (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Vermont-Poultney (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Virginia-A - L (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Virginia-M - Z (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Virginia-Alexandria (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Virginia-Arlington (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Virginia-Charlottesville (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Virginia-Fredericksburg (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Virginia-Hot Springs (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Virginia-Jamestown (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Virginia-James River (Residences, general) (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Virginia-James River (Carter's Grove) (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Virginia-Lorton (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Virginia-Mount Vernon-Exterior Views (prints) (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Virginia-Mount Vernon-Exterior Views (photographs) (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Virginia-Mount Vernon-Interior Views (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Virginia-Mount Vernon-Washington's Tomb (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Virginia-Natural Bridge (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Virginia-Richmond-General (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Virginia-Richmond-Capitol (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Virginia-Richmond-Churches (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Virginia-Richmond-Residences (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Virginia-Stratford (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Virginia-Williamsburg (general) (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Virginia-Williamsburg (residences) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Virginia-Yorktown (Moore House) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Virginia-Yorktown (Nelson House) (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Virginia-Yorktown (general) (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Virginia-Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Washington-A - Z (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Washington-Seattle (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - West Virginia-A - Z (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - West Virginia-Harper's Ferry (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - West Virginia-White Sulphur Springs (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Wisconsin-A-Z (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Wyoming A-Z (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Wyoming- Yellowstone National Park-Geysers (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Wyoming- Yellowstone National Park-Scenery (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Wyoming- Yellowstone National Park-Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous views (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Subseries VIB: AMERICAN VIEWS- FLAT MATERIAL
    - Alabama (Folder FF 524)
    - Alaska (Folder FF 525)
    - Arizona (Folder FF 526)
    - Arkansas (Folder FF 527)
    - California (Folder FF 528 - FF 533)
      FF 530 contains images of Monterey exclusively.
      FF 531 through FF 533 contain images of San Francisco exclusively.
    - Colorado (Folder FF 534 - FF 535)
    - Connecticut (Folder FF 536 - FF 545)
      images arranged alphabetically by city/town.
      FF 542 contains images of Hartford exclusively
      FF 543 and FF 544 contain images of New Haven exclusively.
      FF 545 contains photographs of the Yale campus by Pach Bros., 1885-1886.
    - Delaware (Folder FF 546)
    - District of Columbia (Folder FF 547 - FF 553)
    - Florida (Folder FF 554)
    - Georgia (Folder FF 555)
    - Illinois (Folder FF 556 - FF 559)
    - Indiana (Folder FF 560)
    - Iowa (Folder FF 561)
    - Kansas (Folder FF 562)
    - Kentucky (Folder FF 563)
    - Louisiana (Folder FF 564)
    - Maine (Folder FF 565 - FF 567)
    - Maryland (Folder FF 568 - FF 571)
    - Massachusetts (Folder FF 572 - FF 585)
      FF 580 to FF 585 contain prints of Boston exclusively. FF 585 includes a fictionalized view of Boston by German engraver Franz Xaver Habermann (1721-1796).
    - Michigan (Folder FF 586)
    - Minnesota (Folder FF 587)
    - Mississippi (Folder FF 588)
    - Missouri (Folder FF 589)
    - Montana (Folder FF 590)
    - Nebraska (Folder FF 591)
    - Nevada (Folder FF 592)
    - New Hampshire (Folder FF 593 - FF 594)
    - New Jersey (Folder FF 595 - FF 604)
    - New Mexico (Folder FF 605)
    - New York (Folder FF 606 - FF 668)
      images of New York State, exclusive of New York City, arranged alphabetically by county and/or city. For images of New York City, see Series I-V.
    - North Carolina (Folder FF 669)
    - North Dakota (Folder FF 670)
    - Ohio (Folder FF 671 - FF 678)
    - Oregon (Folder FF 679)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder FF 680 - FF 702)
      FF 690 through FF 702 contain images of Philadelphia exclusively.
    - Rhode Island (Folder FF 703 - FF 708)
    - South Carolina (Folder FF 709 - FF 711)
    - South Dakota (Folder FF 712)
    - Tennessee (Folder FF 713)
    - Texas (Folder FF 714)
    - Utah (Folder FF 715 - FF 716)
    - Vermont (Folder FF 717)
    - Virginia (Folder FF 718 - FF 731)
    - Washington (State) (Folder FF 732)
    - West Virginia (Folder FF 733)
    - Wisconsin (Folder FF 734)
    - Wyoming (Folder FF 735)
  - Subseries VIC: AMERICAN VIEWS - OVERSIZE MATERIAL
    includes images from: California
    Colorado
    Connecticut
    District of Columbia
    Georgia
    Illinois
    Indiana
    Louisiana
    Maine
    Massachusetts
    Missouri
    New Hampshire
    New Jersey
    New York State
    North Carolina
    Ohio
    Pennsylvania
    Rhode Island
    South Carolina.
    The bulk of the material onsists of images of New York State, including Niagara Falls, arranged alphabeticaly by city, county, and/or town.
    - [West Point] (Folder OS FF, Item 2NW / Unit 9B / Bay 27 / Drawer 9)
      [In enclosure with two unrelated photographs.]
- Series VII: Foreign Views
  Series I. Foreign Views is arranged alphabetically by country. Current (as of 2006), and not contemporaneous, names of countries were used. Each country for which there is a view is listed. In the boxed views, if five or more views of a city within a country exist, that city received its own folder.
  - Subseries VIIA: FOREIGN VIEWS - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Austria (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - Algeria (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bahamas (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - Barbados (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - Belgium (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bermuda (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
    - China (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
    - Canada-Alberta-General (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
    - Canada-Alberta-Banff (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
    - Canada-Alberta-British Columbia (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
    - Canada-Alberta-Manitoba (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
    - Canada-Alberta-New Brunswick (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
    - Canada-Alberta-Nova Scotia (Offsite-box 1, Folder 13)
    - Canada-Ontario-General (Offsite-box 1, Folder 14)
    - Canada-Ontario-Ottawa (Offsite-box 1, Folder 15)
    - Canada-Ontario-Toronto (Offsite-box 1, Folder 16)
    - Canada-Quebec-General (Offsite-box 1, Folder 17)
    - Canada-Quebec-Montreal (Offsite-box 1, Folder 18)
    - Canada-Quebec-Quebec City (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
    - Canada-Quebec-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Cuba (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
    - Curacao (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
    - Denmark (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ecuador (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
    - Egypt (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
    - El Salvador (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
    - England (Offsite-box 2, Folder 9)
    - England (election campaign exhibit 1952) (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10)
    - France-General (Offsite-box 2, Folder 11)
    - France-Paris (Offsite-box 2, Folder 12)
    - France-Versailles (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
    - Germany (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
    - Gibraltar (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
    - Greece (Offsite-box 2, Folder 16)
    - Greenland (Offsite-box 2, Folder 17)
    - Guatemala (Offsite-box 2, Folder 18)
    - Haiti (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
    - India (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
    - Israel (Offsite-box 2, Folder 21)
    - Italy-General (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
    - Italy-Naples and Pompeii (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
    - Italy-Venice (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
    - Jamaica (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
    - Japan (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
    - Liberia (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
    - Mexico (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
    - Monaco (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
    - Mozambique (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9)
    - Netherlands-General (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
    - Netherlands-Amsterdam (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
    - New Zealand (Transit of Venus, 1874) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
    - Panama (Offsite-box 3, Folder 13)
    - Philippines (Offsite-box 3, Folder 14)
    - Portugal (Offsite-box 3, Folder 15)
    - Puerto Rico (Offsite-box 3, Folder 16)
    - Russia (Offsite-box 3, Folder 17)
    - Spain (Offsite-box 3, Folder 18)
    - Switzerland-General (and other Alpine views) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 19-20)
    - Switzerland-Davos (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
    - Turkey-General (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
    - Turkey-Armenia, 1919 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
    - United Kingdom-General (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
    - United Kingdom-Channel Islands (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
    - United Kingdom-London (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
    - United Kingdom-Oxford (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    - United Kingdom-Scooby (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subseries VIIB: FOREIGN VIEWS - FLAT MATERIAL
    Arranged alphabetically by country.
  - Subseries VIIC: FOREIGN VIEWS - OVERSIZE
    Two folders. Includes images of:
    Canada
    Cuba
    England
    France
    Japan